龙舌兰酒加奎宁水
Tequila and tonic.
-Ana Lucia  -Jack
上飞机后我们再喝一杯  好么?
We'll have the next drink on the plane, OK?
-我的位置是42F  -42F  好的
-42F.  -42F. Right.
好了  你们全部起来
All right,all of you get up.
Sawyer
能帮我一起做担架么?  我们得抬着他
Help me make a stretcher. We're gonna carry him.
Walt!
-Walt!  -Shannon!
Shannon!
最近怎么样?
So, how you doing?
有个很吵的孩子的那家人已经搬走了
Well, the family with the screaming baby moved.
那你一定很高兴了
Well, you must be thrilled.
事实上...
Actually...
现在又觉得太安静了
it's too quiet now.
那么Danny怎么样?
So, how's Danny?
你们有尝试着和好么?
You two trying to work things out?
没什么好和好的了
There's nothing to work out.
他走了
He left.
你还好吧?
You OK with that?
我想我是那种喜欢独自生活的人
I guess you could say I'm one of those people who's just better off alone.
那么  射击练习还行么?
So how was the firing range?
很好
Good.
再次握枪的感觉怎么样?
How did it feel to hold a gun again?
非常好
Very good.
这些步骤都是必须的  Ana
All these steps count, Ana.
从我们四个月前见面到现在 你已经经历了很多东西
You've come a long way since we met four months ago.
她说  你知道...
She say? You know,
我什么时候能回去工作?
when I can come back to work?
她让我做最后的决定
She left the final determination up to me.
好的
Right.
你觉得你没问题了么?
Do you think you're ready?
你觉得呢?
What do you think?
欢迎你回到警队  Cortez警官
Welcome back to the force,Officer Cortez.
Sayid!
Sayid  不
Sayid, no!
-Eko  放开他  -他是我们中的一个
-Eko, let him go!  -He's one of us!
不
No!
Eko!
不  不
No! No!
Eko!
不  不
No! No!
别动  谁也别动
Don't move! Nobody move!
声明: 本字幕由YYeTs美剧字幕组原创翻译制作
欢迎访问官方论坛  www.YYeTs.net 在线观看 剧情讨论 学习交流
=====本字幕由以下成员荣誉制作 感谢他们的无私奉献======
翻译：skier_airman校对： BillSky
后期：xyz 双语制作：憨妹
========== 字幕总监制：七色九天 ==========
不许动  谁都不准
Nobody move! Nobody!
他身上还有其它东西么?
Does he have anything else on him?
什么?
What?
他刚才拿枪指着你的脖子
He just had a gun to your neck.
去看看他身上还有些什么东西
Check to see if he has anything else on him.
-放下枪  -站住
-Hey. Put it down.  -Stop.
你怎么了  疯了么?  别拿枪指着我
What are you,crazy?Don't point that at me!
-我说了别动  -你到底是怎么了啊?
-I said stop!  -What is your problem,huh?
Ana!
退后
Get back!
你们两个都给我退后
Get back, both of you!
-你疯了么?  -Ana
-Are you crazy?  -Ana
-退下  -Ana
-Now!  -Ana!
我们得把他绑起来
We need to tie him up.
-我不会去绑他  -他刚才想杀你
-I'm not tying him up.  -He tried to kill you.
不
No.
你
You.
你来
You do it.
把他绑起来
Tie him.
用担架上的树藤
Use the vines from the stretcher.
如果我们把担架拆了  我们就无法...
Hey,if we take that thing apart,we won't be able to...
闭嘴
Shut up.
Ana  Sawyer需要看医生  不然他会死的
Ana, Sawyer needs a doctor, or he'll die.
我知道我在做什么
I know what I'm doing.
但愿就这些了
I hope this is all of it.
现在我们也只有这些资料
That's all we've got right now.
好的
Okay.
谢谢  长官
Thanks,captain.
进来吧
Come on in.
看看是谁来了  很高兴见到你 Ana Lucia  欢迎回来
Look who's here. Good to see you,Ana Lucia. Welcome back.
谢谢  Raggs
Thanks, Raggs.
我会把那些资料拿给你的  长官
I'll get you those I.R.S,captain.
-今天之前  -好的
-Today.  -You've got it.
你好么?
How are you?
-很不错  -好的
-Good. Fine.  -Good.
你的职务
Your assignment.
取证部门?  你想让我坐办公桌?
Evidence? You're putting me behind a desk?
-有问题么?  -我想去巡逻
-Is that a problem?  -I want patrol.
-我不在乎你想做什么  -我要坐巡逻车
-I don't care what you want.  -Just put me in a car.
你还在被察看期间  不行
You were in an officer-involved shooting. No.
是因为你是我的上司你才这么做?
You doing this because you're my captain?
还是因为你是我的妈妈?
Or because you're my mother?
两个都是
Both.
拜托让我去巡逻吧
I  need to be back on the street. Please.
如果我让你去巡逻
I put you in a car,
谁都知道是我安排的
everyone's gonna know that I pulled strings.
你不是不想让我对你像对女儿一样么?
You don't want me to treat you like my daughter?
那么就别求我帮你
Don't ask for favors.
那就把我调走
Then transfer me.
我不会调走你的  你去巡逻吧
You don't get the transfer,but I'll give you the car.
开心了么?
Happy?
不好意思打扰一下  长官
Sorry to bother you,captain.
Ana  大房间有你的电话  他们说很重要
Ana, there's a call for you in the bullpen. They say it's real important.
谢谢  Raggs  我马上去接
Thanks, Raggs. I'll be right there.
他们给你准备了一个蛋糕
They got you a cake.
要装作很惊讶的样子
Try and act surprised.
Jack  很高兴在舱子外面见到你
Jack, nice to see you out of the hatch.
你可以多晒会儿太阳了
You could use more sunshine.
我会考虑一下的
I'll take that under advisement.
来点儿水果也许会更好
Little fruit might do you good,too.
对身体有益  至少他们是这么说的
Good for the constitution.Least that's what they say.
如果是他们说的...
Well,if that's what they say.
这些水果你是从哪儿来的?
Where did you get these?
即使你很兴奋也不用还没吞下去就说话啊
Just cos you're excited, no reason to talk with your mouth full.
打过那棵树  我们赌双倍
Past the hanging tree,double or nothing.
你确定?
You sure?
伙计  就赌双倍  你不可能打那么远
There's no way you're hitting it that far.
Hurley  这女人就像打了内固醇
Hurley, the woman's on bloody steroids.
两倍就是一万美元
Double's 10,000 bucks.
那对于一个身家  1亿5千万的人来说并不算什么
That's nothing to someone worth $150 million.
如果你喜欢  他可以给你建一个私人球场
He'll build you your own course if you'd like.
-他说什么?  -别理他  他是个白痴
-What's he talking about?  -Ignore him. He's an idiot.
真该死
Crap!
你打弯了
You hooked it.
试着伸直你的左臂
Try  keeping your left arm straight.
你在给我传授经验?
You're giving me tips?
Kate  我...
Kate, I'm...
我是个医生
I'm a doctor.
所以你认为你可以打得更好?
So you think you could do better?
谁都可以击球  但那不是高尔夫
Anyone can hit a ball.That's not golf.
那么什么才是高尔夫?
And what's golf?
高尔夫讲求精确性
Golf is accuracy.
那么我们来比几个洞试试?
Well, why don't we play a few holes
比比我们俩谁更精确?
and see which one of us is more accurate?
你在开玩笑  是么?
You're kidding, right?
三个洞  不设标准杆  谁赢谁才有权说大话
Three holes,no handicap.We play for bragging rights.
我们还等什么?
What are we waiting for?
Ana  我们快去他们的营地吧  那只是一场意外
Ana, let's just get to their camp.It was an accident.
他们会理解的
They'll understand.
他们会理解的?我杀了他们中的一个
They'll understand?I killed one of them.
-这两人想动你就喊  -等等  你想干...
-Those two move? Shout.  -Wait. What are you do...
放开我
Untie me.
-我不会...  -放开我
-I'm not gonna...  -Untie me!
Ana!
你做什么?
What are you doing?
我把他带回他的营地
I'm taking him back to his camp.
别走  求你了
Don't leave. Please.
如果你和他互换  他是不会救你的
If that were you,he'd let you die.
我不是为了他才这么做的
I'm not doing it for him.
我是为了我自己
I'm doing it for me.
那个心理医生给了你什么好药?
So that shrink give you any good drugs?
不是那种心理医生
Not that kind of shrink.
-你想我么?  -伙计  当然
-Did you miss me?  -Boy, did I.
听说了你和Danny的事了
Heard about you and Danny.
想让我去踢他两脚么?
Want me to go kick his ass for you?
不用了
Nah.
现在这样很好
It's better this way.
我们来这儿做什么?
What are we doing in Westwood?
这儿风景很好
Thought a change of scenery would be nice.
好风景和好治安来欢迎你的回归
Nice,safe neighborhood for your first day back.
-这是她的主意  是么?  -她是上司
-This was her idea, wasn't it?  -She is the captain.
呼叫亚当809号  有一起家庭骚乱事件等待处理  在2210街区
8-adam-9,please respond to a domestic disturbance call. 2210 south veteran.
-这是亚当816号  -那不是呼叫我们的
-This is 8-adam-16.  -That's not our call.
我们离事件地点不到三个街区  我们会去处理
We're just three blocks away from that call on veteran. We got it.
收到  亚当816号
Copy that,8-adam-16.
你要去哪儿?  你在做什么?
Where are you going?!What are you doing?!
不是电视机  Travis  这电视机是我的
Not the TV,Travis. The tv is mine!
滚吧  这是我拿钱买的
Like hell it is!I bought it with my money!
骗子
Liar!
-是你叫的警察?  -什么?
-Did you call the cops?!  -What?!
做点有价值的事吧  Shawna  别瞎来
Huh?! Do something useful, Shawna. Shut your trap!
逮捕他  他偷了我的电视机
Arrest him! He is stealing my TV!
-她打了我  她打了我  -他不能把电视机带走
-She hit me! She hit me!  -He cannot get away with it!
够了  你们两个
Hey, enough, both of you!
你想干什么?  把孩子带走?
What are you gonna do? Take the baby?
-让这该死的孩子别吵了  -不
-Shut the damn kid up!  -No!
你们两个停下
Both of you!
把手放在背后
Put your hands where I can see them!
趴下
Get down on the ground.
Cortez警官
Officer Cortez!
太太  把你的孩子带到楼上去
Ma'am, get your baby upstairs.
Ana lucia!
把手放在地上
Get your hands on the ground!
Ana lucia!
他已经趴下了
He's down.
好  好  我趴下  我趴下
Okay, okay. I'm down, I'm down.
马上收好你的武器
Holster your weapon. Now.
我想你应该放了他
I think you should let him go.
不  他会报复我的
No. He's gonna come after me.
你怎么知道
You don't know that.
我杀了他爱的人
I killed someone he loves.
马上坐下
Sit down. Now.
我给他点水喝
I'm bringing him water
你想向我开枪?
You gonna shoot me?
开枪吧
Shoot me.
你别想放开他
Don't even think of untying him.
那女人是谁?
Who is that woman?
她叫Ana Lucia  她是飞机上的
Her name is Ana Lucia. She was on the plane.
他们全都是尾舱的
Tail section. They all were.
我们带他们回来的
We were bringing them back.
Walt呢?
Where is Walt?
他们带走了他
They took him.
其它人
The others.
怎么回事  他们带走了他?
What do you mean, they took him?
从竹筏上带走的  就在我们离开的那个晚上
From the raft.The night we left.
伙计...
man...
我们会想办法放开你的  伙计
Hey,we're gonna get out of this,man.
你先来
Guess you're first.
真幸运
Lucky me.
在我俱乐部里 女子发球区往往会前推10英尺  所以如果你...
You know,the ladies' tee at my club back home is about 10 feet closer,so if you...
闭嘴  Jack
Shut up, Jack.
好球
Nice.
该你了
You're up.
你还真把球打到那儿去了
You really put it in there.
我们还有球  你可以选择抛球
We have more balls.You could always just take a drop.
不用了
I'm good.
找到了
Got it.
你最好躲开点
You may want to move.
什么?
What?
医生在哪儿?
Where is the doctor?
我拉着他  我拉着他
I got him. I got him.
-好的  我们去哪儿?  -浴室
-Okay. Where are we headed?  -Bathroom.
他烧得很厉害  我们得给他冲个澡
He's burning up. We've got to get him in the shower
让他降降温
and bring his fever down.
我能做什么?
What can I do?
你去医药箱里找找  那儿有一瓶氧氟沙星
Okay. Go through the medical stash. There's a bottle of Ofloxacin.
-氧氟沙星  -氧氟沙星  白色的小药片
-Ofloxacin.  -Ofloxacin, little white pills.
再带一些酒精和纱布过来
Bring the alcohol and some gauze patches,
然后给床铺上干净的床单
and strip that bed, make sure it's got clean sheets on it.
-Kate  -好的  好的
-Kate!  -Uh, yeah. Yeah.
发生了什么事?
What happened?
John... 快按按键
John... the button.
你好
Hello.
我们在这儿干什么  Ana?
What are we doing here, Ana?
我是说  他们的营地已经很近了
I mean, their camp has gotta be close.
我想尽快回到我妻子那儿去
I just want to get back to my wife.
我让你在这儿活了多久  Bernard?
How long have I kept you alive out here, Bernard?
那就好了
That's right.
让我安静会儿
So cut me some slack.
我们只想知道你在干什么  你有什么计划?
Hey. We just want to know what you're doing. What's the plan?
她没有计划
She has no plan!
她只有负罪感...和一把抢
She only has her guilt...and a gun.
你要计划是么?
You want a plan?
你们的营地里有子弹么?
Do you have any ammo back at your camp?
-什么?  -这把枪的子弹
-What?  -Ammo for the gun.
你们营地里有么?
Do you have any back at your camp?
有  有几盒
Yeah, a couple boxes.
好的  我要了  至少要一半
All right. I want it. At least half.
我还要一个包裹  一个大包
And I'll need a pack. A big one.
一条毯子  一些药品
A blanket. Some medicine.
衣服  牛仔裤和袜子
Clothes jeans and socks.
-你都记住了么?  -记住了
-You getting all this?  -Yeah, I got it.
好的  你把那些东西带来给我
All right. You bring all of that stuff back to me,
我就放了你的朋友
and I'll let your friend go.
我是不会离开他的
I'm not leaving him.
-Michael  你得这么做  -不  我们呆在一起
-Michael, you should.  -No. We stay together.
走
Go.
我会回来的  伙计
I'll be back,man.
Ana  你干什么?  你不能一个人生活在这儿
Ana, what are you doing? You can't live out here alone.
我已经是一个人了
I'm already alone.
我来签出
I'll sign us out.
什么  你现在和我说话了?
What,you're talking to me now?
我只是想回家  AL
I just want to go home, A.L.
我让那家伙停下已经叫了两次了
Hey, I ordered that guy to stop twice.
那么这就是说每次我们
So does that mean every time we run into some
碰上拿着电视机的混混  我们就要把他放倒?
with a tv in his hands,you're gonna draw down?
Ana Lucia  你要的人...我们抓到了
Hey, Ana Lucia, your guy...we got him.
他叫Jason McCormack
His name is Jason McCormack.
我们抓他时他正在埃克公园  袭击一个老妇女
We picked him upon an assault on an elderly woman in Echo Park.
他的指纹部分与你在  犯罪现场取得的吻合
His fingerprints match the partial from your crime scene.
我们审问过他了  他供认了
We questioned him, and he confessed.
地方检察官已经准备控告他 现在就差你的指认了
The D.A.'S ready to file charges. All he needs is for you to I.D. him.
-不是他  -他已经供认了
-It's not him.  -He confessed.
我不认识他
I don't know him.
我们想单独谈谈
Can you guys give us a minute?
你为什么这么做?
Why are you doing this?
因为这不是他
Because it's not him.
他向你开了四枪...你防弹背心上有四个枪眼
He put four bullets into you...hollow points through your vest.
他想杀了你
He tried to kill you.
你想知道他的前科么?
You want a list of his priors?
你想把这个家伙放回大街上去?
You want to put this guy back out on the street?
这不是他
It's not him.
发生了什么事?
What happened?
那儿发生了什么事?
Out there. What happened?
发生了一场意外
There was an accident.
什么意外?
What kind of accident?
一个女子中弹了...
A girl was shot...
死了
and killed.
她长得怎样?
What did she look like?
她很高  金发
She was tall, with blond hair.
-还有一个阿拉伯男人...  -是Shannon
-There was an Arab man...  -Shannon.
你说你们那伙儿有5人?
You said there were five of you from the tail section?
-4个  -4个
-Four.  -Four.
那为什么余下那几个不和你一起回来?
Why didn't the rest of them come back with you?
还有Michael和Jin呢?
And Michael,Jin.
他们现在还不能回来
They cannot come back right now.
你能带我去他们那儿么?
Can  you take me to them?
不行
No.
给你
Here you go.
怎么了?  他为什么抖个不停?
What's happening? Why is he shaking?
他得了败血症
He's septic.
感染已经侵入血液循环了
The infection's gotten into the bloodstream.
如果抗生素不能退烧  他会休克的
If the antibiotics don't bring the fever down,he'll go into shock.
扶住他
Hold him up.
好了
Okay,I got him.
吞下去  吞下去  吞下去  该死
Swallow it. Swallow it. Swallow it. Damn it.
-让我来吧  -不不  我来
-Here, I'll do it.  -No, no, I got it.
我能行的
I can do it.
Sawyer...
我是Kate
it's Kate.
你得听我说  好么?
You need to listen to me, okay?
只有你吞下了这颗药丸你才能好
The only way that you are gonna get better is if you take this pill.
所以你得吞下它  好么?
So I need you to swallow it, okay?
好的  我们开始吧
Okay, here we go.
好了  吞下去
Now swallow.
吞下吧
Swallow.
好的  好的  非常好
Good. Good. That's good.
干得好
Nice job.
我从没在医学院学过耳语治疗
Never learned the whole whisper-in-the-earthing in med school.
你要干什么?
What are you doing?
我要走了  Ana
I'm going, Ana.
我不想再这么呆下去了
I don't want to be a part of this.
我了解你为我们做的一切
I know everything you've done for us.
并且如果不是你我根本不可能活下来 但是我要走了
And I wouldn't even be alive if it weren't for you. But I'm going.
你呢?
What about you?
我只是认为你的性格不太好
I just don't think you're the best judge of character.
你把Nathan扔进坑里这件事我倒是很赞同的
I was with you when you put Nathan in the pit.
好吧
All right.
你想走是么?  那么走吧
You want to go? Go.
都走吧
Leave.
你...
You...
也走
go.
离开这儿
Get outta here.
走
Go.
Michael!
Sun
没事的  Jin很好
It's all right. Jin is okay.
发生了什么事?  他在哪儿?
What happened? Where is he?
他没事  我会解释的
He's fine, and I'll explain.
但是现在我得找到Jack
But right now I need to find Jack.
他们在哪儿?
Where are they?
我说了...他们在哪儿?
I said... where are they?
-Jack  这不是他的错... -Shannon死了  我不...
-Jack, it's not his fault...  -Shannon's dead! I'm not...
你得马上把我带回那儿去
You're gonna take me back out there right now.
问题不在他身上  他把Sawyer带回来了
This man isn't the problem. He brought Sawyer back.
已经半死了  肩上还有个枪眼  John
Half-dead, with a bullet hole through his shoulder, John!
你是想和我说话  还是就坐在那儿?
Are you gonna talk to me, or are you just gonna sit there?
我说的一切都会使你更生气
Anything I say will only make you angry.
那么  是的  我就坐在这儿
So, yes, I will sit here.
Jack!
Jack! Jack!
Michael.
我们遇到麻烦了  伙计
We got a problem,man.
你记得怎么回到那儿去  是么?
You remember how to get out there, right?
我想是的
I think so.
我们得停下来好好想想  Jack
We should stop and think about this, Jack
想什么  John?  Shannon死了
Think about what, John? Shannon's dead.
Sayid正在枪口上
Sayid's being held at gunpoint.
你是想呆在这儿期盼事情自己解决么?
You want to sit here and hope that situation resolves itself?
那就随你吧
You be my guest.
-知道怎么用么?  -应该吧
-Know how to use this?  -Guess so.
站住
Stop!
拜托
Please.
你想要什么?
What do you want?
什么?
Excuse me?
和平?  复仇? 公正?  你就是要拿着枪来解决问题么?
Peace? Revenge? Justice? And you are going out with all these guns.
你想要什么?
What do you want?
我要我们的人安全回来
I want all of our people back here safely.
-你的朋友谋杀了...  -Ana Lucia犯了个错误
-Your friend murdered...  -Ana Lucia made a mistake.
你说什么?
What did you say?
Ana Lucia犯了个错误
Ana Lucia made a mistake.
Ana Lucia.
我带你去那儿
I will take you there.
但是只能带你一个人去
But only you.
并且不能带枪
And no guns.
我们走吧
Let's go.
你是哪儿人?
Where you from?
Where are you from?
伊拉克
I am from Iraq.
你有孩子么?
You have any kids?
你为什么这么问?
Why are you asking me if I have children?
我很好奇
I'm curious.
我没有  你有么?
I do not. Do you have children?
没有
No.
你会杀了我么?
Are you going to kill me?
你现在就在想这个问题  是么?
That's what you're thinking about, isn't it?
我需要么?
Should I?
大约40天前  在这个岛上
Almost 40 days ago, on this very island,
我把一个男人绑在树上拷问他
I tied a man to a tree,and I tortured him.
我折磨他就像我折磨的许多人一样...
I tortured him, as I've tortured many men...
晚上那些人的声音还回响在我耳畔
men whose voices I still hear at night.
你该杀我么?
Should you kill me?
也许你该这么做
Maybe you should.
也许你正打算这么做
Maybe you were meant to.
我是个警察
I'm a cop.
我曾是个警察
Well... I was a cop.
一个晚上  我和我的搭档  去处理一起入室行窃案件
One night, my partner and I responded to a burglary call.
我们是第一个到达那儿的
We were the first ones there.
我在前门守着  他去后面察看
I covered the front,and he went around the back.
过了一会儿
I was there a minute.
那个孩子从前门出来了
Then this kid comes right through the front door.
我叫他把手举起来
I tell him to put his hands up.
但他说我弄错了
And he says I'm making a mistake,
他还是个学生
that he's a student.
而且他想给我看他的身份证
And he wants to show me his I.D.
我相信了
I believed him.
我就...
I just...
我就让他过来了
I let him reach.
然后就是一声枪响
All I remember was a pop.
我倒地的时候我以为我已经死了
By the time I hit the ground, I thought I was dead.
我觉得我死了
I feel dead.
那个人后来怎样了...那个向你开枪的人?
What happened to him...the man who shot you?
Jason.
我认识你?
I know you?
我那时怀孕了
I was pregnant.
他后来怎样了?
What happened to him?
不知道  他们没抓住他
Nothing. They never found him.
来吧
Go ahead.
捡起来
Pick it up.
这是我应得的报应
I deserve it.
杀了你又有什么好处...
What good would it be to kill you...
如果我们已经都死了呢?
if we're both already dead?
能听见我说话么?
Can you hear me?
你会好起来的
You're gonna be okay.
你会没事的
You're gonna be all right.
你回家了
You're home.
==============|  YYeTs字幕组招募启示  |==============
英文字幕录制(居住在加拿大和美国)  双语字幕校正   时间轴调整
英语翻译   欧美影视新闻翻译  影视评论  论坛版主  美工人员
服务器提供者  发布宣传  联系地址：www.YYeTs.com
==== YYeTs属于网络爱好者组织 加入者仅凭个人兴趣爱好 无报酬 ====